techpatio.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy — TechPatio

## Cookies, ‘Web Beacons’ and Visitor Data Tracking

We may place a ‘cookie’ on your computer or create a unique “session id” for purposes of remembering your preferences, pages viewed, etc. We doe not use cookies or session ID’s for ‘tracking’ purposes or for gathering any personally identifiable information about you. If you choose, you may disable cookies in your web-browser to prevent use of such cookies. We use a combination of web-server logs and third-party analytical data gathering tools for the purposes of aggregate visitor traffic information which may set a cookie on your computer. The data collected by these third-party services may include information such as your IP address, type of web-browser, and computer operating system.

Currently we use the following third-party visitor tracking tools:

We do not use “web beacons” of any kind with the exception of third-party links or advertisers (see next section).

We might use the services of Tynt.com to automatically add a “read more”-link to all copied texts from TechPatio.com.

## Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

We allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on our websites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. We doe not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks. The advertiser(s) may also use information regarding your use of our websites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

## IP Addresses and Logging

We log visitors IP addresses on some of our websites. We do this because to make sure they are not a bot but a real person. We do not give this information to any third parties.

### Comments & Leave a Comment

comments
